B2.
Simon is listening to a weather forecast for the four cities in part B1, listen with him and complete the table below.
Good morning and welcome to world weather today.
We start in Moscow on a cold and snowy December morning.
The temperature is minus 10 to minus 5 degrees Celsius, so wear lots of warm clothes when you go outside.
Next we head over to Shanghai on a sunny morning.
The temperature is 7 to 9 degrees Celsius and there's a cool wind, so wear a light scarf.
Now we move to bright and sunny Cairo.
The temperature is 14 to 16 degrees Celsius, so it's fine to wear a light jacket.
And finally, it's an unusual day in Sydney because it's raining.
It's still hot with a temperature of 26 to 29 degrees Celsius, but you'll need your umbrella if you go outside. That's it.
Have a great day!